<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dating Application</string>
    <string name="welcome">Dream-Date Profile</string>
    <string name="notifying_service_controller"><b>This service will update a status bar notification
     every 15 seconds for a minute</b></string>
     <string name="start_service">Start Service</string>
     <string name="stop_service">Stop Service</string>
     <string name="status_bar_chennai">chennai</string>
     <string name="status_bar_salem">Salem</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_ok_message">I am ok</string>
     <string name="status_bar_coimbatore">Coimbatore</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_clear">Clear notification</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_mood_title">Matching</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_icons_only">Icons only</string>
     <string name="status_bar_erode">Erode</string>
     <string name="status_bar_madurai">Madurai</string>
     <string name="status_bar_nellai">Tirunelvelli</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_icons_and_marquee">Icons and marquee</string>
     <string name="status_bar_notifications_remote_views">Use remote views in balloon</string>
     <string name="userinfo"> User </string>
     <string name="local_service_started">Local service has started</string>
     <string name="local_service_stopped">Local service has stopped</string>

    <!--   partner profile    -->
    <string name="textage">Expected Age:</string>
    <string name="textheight">Expected Height:</string>
    <string name="textweight">Expected Weight:</string>
    <string name="partner"> Specify the partner profile: This will help  others to have some idea of what you want. Please fill all the fields  that are an absolutely  must and  desirable.
    </string>

   <!-- Matching Profile   -->

    <string name="repeating_received">If your expected Dream-mate profile
                  found then you will receive notification every 10 seconds.</string>

    <string name="repeating_scheduled">Dream mate found! Ready to chat now.</string>
    <string name="repeating_unscheduled">stop service</string>
    <string name="profile1">SWEETY,FEMALE,23,155 cm,55Kg,St.ThomasMount</string>
    <string name="profile2">BABLI,FEMALE,18,156 cm,56Kg,TNagar-Renganathan Street</string>
    <string name="profile3">LOLO,FEMALE,19,157 cm, 57Kg,TNagar-Panagalpark</string>
    <string name="profile4">AISH,FEMALE,21,158 cm, 45Kg,Adyar</string>

    <!-- Main Profile   -->
    <string name="help"><b>Need to find your dreamdate on your mobile? Follow these steps.</b></string>
    <string name="helpprofile">Your Profile : First you need to fill your profile and this profile might be communicated to the matches if you wish so.</string>
    <string name="helppartner">Dream-date Profile: You must fill out a dream-date profile. This  the kind of
                  profile that you request for dating. More than 1 dream-date profile can be stored, and the
                  Dating application will store this in your device locally. This information will also send
                  to the Dating server.</string>
     <string name="helpservice">Service : Dating service runs in the background looking for dating matches for you.
                   The service also listens for incoming messages from the Dating server and uses an
                   appropriate notification service to inform you.</string>
     <string name="helpalert">Alerts : A Dating notifier will run along with the Dating service. This
                   notifier will alert you of all dating matches found. The dating alert will specify
                   Proximity and the Closeness of the Match. The Dating alert will use LBS, Maps and all
                   kinds of locational api's to interact with you. </string>
     <string name="helpinteraction">Interaction : You can interact with the matches in your own way. You
                   can select one or more matches and communicate with the match in an anonymous way. You can
                   save all the matching profiles in your mobile device locally for future communication.
                   Also you can delete this matching information at anytime.</string>
     <string name="helpbroadcast">Location Broadcast : The dating service will be broadcasting your locations
                   to the dating server when you are on move. This location information need not be sent,
                   if you don't want. The polling interval can be set by you to broadcast your location every 5 minutes and you can also totally turn off this feature.</string>
</resources>